PROJECT SILENCE
Securing the captives' location is
no guarantee a rescue will succeed.
THE NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL
We can't lose more men for nothing.
We have to buy time. At least a month.
Let's impose a press embargo,
and quietly pursue negotiations.
What? A month?
Good grief, you're
Secretary of Security.
What if they kill all the
captives while we waste time?
What do other secretaries think?
What's that?
Speak for yourself.
I'm Jung-won Cha,
Deputy Security Director.
What's unique about this case
is they've made no request
to talk in five months,
which suggests two possibilities.
One,
the terrorists are trying to raise the
ransom by delaying negotiations.
Two, the captives are already dead,
so there's no leverage for negotiation.
Either the captives are dead
or we wait for talks to happen.
So no need to rescue them?
Let's not jeopardize the Secretary's
ratings for the presidency, huh?
With so much uncertainty,
it would be unwise to risk
damaging this administration
considering the upcoming election.
Sir, it simply amounts to dereliction
of our duty as public officials.
It's a nation's duty
to protect its citizens no
matter where they are.
Our duty is to serve the half
of the nation that supports us.
That majority expects wiser political
judgment from this government.
How dare a mere deputy director
preach about political judgment?
Have you ever considered
how this affects their families?
Is your approval rating that important?
Good day.
Hey.
Pretty bold of you to talk
to ministers so brazenly
I don't care about that. Only
about winning this election.
If I had two more men like you,
I'd be the President already.
You're almost there now
You will be. The President.
Doesn't your aspiring
rapper leave today?
Yeah.
You did a good job
raising her on your own.
- I appreciate it, but I can't.
- Just take it.
I can't.
I know how tough it was raising
her alone while looking after me.
So it's my wise political judgment.
Just take it.
The sooner the better.
Actually. Saturday works better...
Thanks.
Great. I'll see you then.
...experiments were conducted
on the two surviving samples,
Statistics reveal over 3 million animals
were used for lab testing since last year...
Did you have to go this far?
Selling the house too?
To afford you studying
abroad, we have to.
Be on your best
behavior with your aunt.
Study, no rapping.
Why did you pack mom's book?
Why take something you don't need?
You don't get to decide
what I need or don't.
Yes, I do. Because I'm your dad.
- Work with me here, please?
- It's the last copy of her book.
...leading the runner-up
by a landslide.
- Chung is topping the poll.
- Okay. Go get him.
Chung is sailing off in taking
the next presidential office.
Due to the still atmosphere
a fog warning has been issued,
with a high chance of thick fog
building up along the west coast.
Drivers passing through the
area, please take extra care.
LAST GAS STATION BEFORE AIRPORT
Did you two fight?
Was it a mother-daughter row?
You mean father-daughter?
- Hey... hey!
- How much...
He should grab a nap,
at least a short one.
If you see that truck
on the way, stay clear.
That driver played poker all night,
so avoid him if you want to live.
- How much do I owe you?
- $64.40.
Our card reader's not working.
- Can you pay cash?
- I don't have any on me.
Oh, sure you do.
Alright, fine. I'll give
you a little discount.
I have cash.
You're a tow truck driver, right?
No. I work here at the gas station.
Why would a pump attendant
carry a master key?
Huh?
It's illegal to unlock a car even
for a wrecker driver, you know.
Uh... Hey. Well.
Fine. Give me your
card. I'll see if it works.
Forget it.
Tell the owner I'll pay him
directly on my way back.
What...? Are you for real? Hey!
Dad. You can't leave without paying.
This punk won't rip me off.
Pulling a trick on me?
Hey! Hey, you! $64.40.
- I'll take care of it. Don't worry.
- Hey! Hey!
Thank God we live close
to the airport, right?
We can get an emergency passport
when the office opens in the morning,
then get the first flight out.
Miran...
Forget the tournament.
I still have a lot to learn about
being your tour manager.
Don't give me a long excuse about
forgetting to renew my passport.
I'm tired of your lame excuses.
I'll pull out of the tournament.
- Come on, Yura. I'm really sorry.
- Excuse me!
But you're... right?
Oh, you must be a golf fan.
Yes. It's Yura.
She hasn't been on TV much lately.
Come on, Yura. Give
the lady an autograph.
- Don't get ahead of yourself.
- Golf?
I thought you were my cousin.
- You look so much like her.
- Honey?
I've been looking all over for you.
Come on, we'll miss the bus.
It's chilly, huh?
Put this on. You'll catch a cold.
Honey, be careful!
Sweetheart..
Ma'am.
- That was close.
- That crazy driver!
Are you okay?
It's me. Your husband.
Thank you. Hold my hand, darling.
Oh, that lady must be senile.
Hush up, Miran.
This visibility is the
worst. This is unreal.
What's unreal is that it's
just the two of us on duty.
Go on a patrol.
Being on call on a day
like this... Just my luck.
Oh God, what's this?
Yura, what's all this?
It's called fog, alright?
Is it really fog? It's so thick.
It can't be anything else.
What should I do?
Pull over until it passes?
What for? Just drive normally
like everyone else.
Oh my God...
Come on, buddies.
If you don't call it.
I could really die.
Oh! Thank you! Thank you!
What the hell?
It takes about 20 minutes
to the Incheon Lab.
It's been an honor working with you.
Vehicle 1, entering the Airport Bridge.
- Where's this?
- It's Vietnam, two days ago.
How come I look like an old lady here?
Are you okay?
Fuck!
What's going on?
This... cannot be real.
Thank goodness for my
fabulous driving skills.
- You okay, Miran?
- Are you okay? What's going on?
There's been a pileup in
the Seoul-bound lanes.
It's massive. What should I do?
I can see it from here.
How's the airport side?
Unaffected.
What's that?
Don't fuck with me! Give me my $64.40.
I'm telling the truth!
A major pileup on the Airport Bridge...
Beware of the fog on your way out.
The bastard must be stuck there.
I'm going out there to get your money.
- What the... Come here, you bastard!
- Trust me, I'll be back.
Just give me my money.
Let's go, Jodie!
I'm not done with you.
Come here you thief!
Switching to the second lane.
Check.
This looks real bad. Be careful. Dad.
Caution ahead.
What's he doing?
Dad, look out!
Commander! Sir!
It's Goo, not Boo... As in Google.
Oh no... I'll fix it. As good as new.
How are you going to do that?
Fix the damn car instead.
No. We're on the bridge.
The Airport Bridge.
Hey, man. Did Kyung-min leave safely?
Hello, sir. I'm on the
Airport Bridge right now.
On our way, there was a massive
pileup due to thick fog.
This will be tomorrow's news headline.
You better come to the scene before
they criticize our late response.
Give me the location.
I'll be there ASAP.
Yes, sir.
Dad... There was a flipped car.
Aren't you going to help?
Hey. What are you doing?
I'll go check. You stay put, okay?
Go check on the dogs.
Are you okay?
Come in. Come in, V-1.
Can you hear me, V-1?
Respond. Come in, V-1,
Hey.
Check for yourself. You, too.
- Please stay with the doctor.
- What?
Where in the hell are we?
Jam the cell signal on the bridge.
Yes, Commander.
We're 10.4 km in the airport direction.
Yes.
Hello?
What the...?
SERVICE NOT AVAILABLE
- There's no signal?
- Hello? Hello?
Hey, Kyung...
Kyung-min!
Where did she go? Kyung-min!
Hey... Stop that.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
Do you want this? Take it.
E9.
Is that your name? Here, it's for you.
Kyung-min!
What the hell are you doing?
It's dangerous.
I think it's hurt.
Even so, don't touch it.
You don't know that dog.
It's bleeding from the head.
Ugh, she thinks she's the boss.
It's just a club. I'll
straighten it back.
What's that?
Oh, I hate dogs. Don't come near me.
- Did you check on them?
- The Echoes have escaped.
What?
The order just came to
activate the control program.
- What... now? Here?
- Yes, Doctor.
- Wait.
- Step back.
I need to know what's going on.
A helicopter will arrive
soon. Get on it.
Wait a minute. A helicopter?
In this visibility?
That's against flight protocol.
State your military branch.
Who are you? Who the hell are you?
I'm Department of Security
at the Blue House.
Did you jam the cell phone signal?
This is an emergency.
I ask for your cooperation.
What emergency? Are
you escorting the President?
If not, I won't cooperate.
Shut down the jamming.
Fucking bureaucrat...
He just won't shut up.
What the hell?
You bastards...
- This is an active operation.
- How dare you! Get off me.
- Dad?
- What do you think you're doing?
- You lunatics!
- Dad!
- Hey, kid.
- Hey! Don't!
- Stand back.
- What are you doing?
Don't worry, Kyung-min. Daddy's fine.
All hell broke loose here.
What should we do, Jodie?
I can't see a thing... there he is.
Here! Over here. Stop. Stop.
- Okay, fine.
- Stop.
You're hard at work.
Can you tow my car
first? I'm in a hurry.
I can do it quick if you pay double.
Fine. Just do it.
Okay.
When will you release him?
When the boys get back.
Uncuff me while I'm being nice.
Don't try to be smart.
I'll make you regret it.
Regret is something
I live with every day.
If this goes haywire,
then we're all dead.
So, stop interrupting me.
You're safest with me.
Inputting target now.
Emergency code #04. Project Silence.
Configuring a new target.
Guideline one.
This code may be issued
to control the Echoes
and enable damage
control by their handlers.
Target configured.
Starting in...
three, two, one.
What are you doing?
- I asked what you're doing.
- Quiet! You want to die?
Why isn't she moving?
We don't have control on E9.
We got the rest of the pack,
so I'm stopping the program.
Locate the transport vehicle.
We've located the vehicle.
We'll lower the cage from
its current position.
Be ready to move.
Locate the transport vehicle.
What's that?
Jodie?
Where are you going, my girl?
- Where are you going, man?
- No, Jodie! Come back here.
State your branch, and what is
going on with those mad dogs.
You have five minutes to explain.
Why don't you ask your superior
about the Silence Project?
- What?
- The Silence Project.
Transfer the retrieved
Echoes first. Move fast.
This is an active operation.
You can't be here.
Shut down the damn jammer.
How else can I report to my boss?
- Let me go!
- Step back.
What's that mutt doing there?
- You can't go past.
- Jodie! She's my family, bastards!
- Jodie!
- Please leave.
Jodie!
- Come here, Jodie!
- You can't, sir.
- Get rid of that thing.
- Yes, sir.
- You there.
- Come here.
- Kyung-min! What are you doing?
- You can't be here, kid.
- Let go of her.
- Who are you?
You! Hey
$64.40, right?
Bring over Jodie and my money. Now!
Echo 9 is not moving.
I'll take care of E9 later.
Hoist up the cage.
You just saw me, right? Let me go.
You can't go through.
Oh, geez.
Something's wrong.
It's still there.
Hoisting up the cage now.
E9's control chip has fallen out.
I repeat. E9's control chip
has been detached.
Lieutenant.
What's that?
This could trigger an error response.
The dogs will go out of control again.
Stay here. Don't wander off.
What the hell are you up to?
Tell me straight.
The dogs are out of control again.
- What?
- It's not my fault.
Dad.
Kyung-min!
Why is it coming here?
Do you know that dog?
Run!
Miran!
Yura!
Run, Miran.
Down!
Step on it!
Get in, in.
Hurry!
Hey!
Dad, that's the guy from earlier.
The bastard left me here to die.
Goddamn murderer.
What are you doing? We can take him.
What are you doing?
We can take him, Dad.
You okay, Jodie? I'm sorry.
We can live. We'll live.
Let's go!
Mister!
Driver.
$64.40! You drove
right past us, murderer.
How can you step on the gas
when you see a person in danger?
You better step on it
now. Yeah, step on it.
Harder!
Shit! Fire, fire!
Jodie, go bite that man.
Hey, are you driving
with your eyes closed?
Shit, this man's dead.
Move the car now.
Ugh, blood. Bastard.
Jodie.
Papa's gonna die out here.
Who'll take care of you after I'm gone?
Damn it.
You scared me, asshole.
Can anyone hear me? Please respond.
Can anyone hear me?
What the hell is that?
What's that? On its snout?
Who jammed the signal?
It was a military decision.
What? When is the fog likely to clear?
No idea until sunrise.
No rescue chopper can
be dispatched until then.
And a military cargo has crashed.
And access from the sea?
Can't you get civilian boats
underneath the bridge?
The bridge is 70m above sea level.
Plus, it's low tide so
ships just can't approach.
Geez.
What's up with the dogs?
There he comes.
- I'll debrief you in a moment.
- Any update on the rescue?
Is it true there's a risk the
bridge might collapse?
Why is the network blocked?
Do you have an estimate of casualties?
We're employing all means
possible in order to save lives.
If it gets inside, we're all dead meat.
Back off the car now.
Open your mouth again,
and I'll open the trunk.
I swear to God.
Go on then, murderer!
Go ahead and murder me.
- I'll do it.
- Go on.
Because if you don't open
it, I'll kill you myself.
- Please, don't open it. I beg you.
- It's okay... It's okay...
Please, don't open the trunk.
Wake him up.
Excuse me?
That doctor next to you. Wake him up!
Yes, I'll do my best, sir. Hey!
Man, you better wake up.
Come on, we're here.
Shouldn't we help those people?
Let's not be rash. They might be dead.
We won't know that unless we check.
She's right. They're alive.
Right?
The dogs are lingering around.
Do you know how many people
were killed by your mad dogs?
I developed rescue dogs
that respond to human voices.
But the military made me
reprogram them for hunting.
For what purpose? Why?
The U.S. and European countries
commissioned us
to develop killer canines
to hunt terrorists.
They're trained to recognize any
target's voice and attack them.
But the project was scrapped
due to serious issues.
Then, what are they
doing on the bridge?
We were disposing of
the failed samples today.
But they got loose
during transportation.
Who's in charge of the program?
I'm only a researcher. I only
did what was requested.
I'm not responsible.
You made them go mad? Fucking psychos!
If a dog goes mad, it's on the owner,
Cut out the dog crap.
Can I have some water, please?
Please respond. Can anyone hear me?
I'm Jung-won Cha,
Department of Security.
Where are you?
You okay, man?
We're okay for now.
We're near the main tower.
There's a tanker in front of us.
Get out of there right now.
It's carrying toxic gas.
The rescue team is getting ready.
Listen. Have you heard
of the Silence Project?
Yes, just now.
I'm with the researcher
who developed the project.
Apparently, it's some
fucked-up fantasy scenario.
Once I get out, we can take down
any related military personnel and
that damn Defense Minister, too.
I have the key witness statement.
If it doesn't get tracked back to us,
it'll all go well for us.
Listen to me carefully.
This is connected to us.
The project was approved
by the Blue House
in the early days after taking office.
- What?
- Do you understand what I'm saying?
You okay, man? Jung-won!
Smoke's getting in.
Come here, Jodie.
- They're telling us to get on.
- You're right.
Cover your mouth, Kyung-min.
No matter what, don't breathe.
We'll run on three. Run
back to the bus, okay,
I'm depending on you
to open the trunk, sir.
Hold your breath, Jodie.
One... Dammit!
Dammit, who ran out first?
- Open the trunk, hurry!
- Get out, Kyung-min.
Let's go.
- Dad!
- Go on, baby!
Go. Run!
Sir, you need to dispatch
SWAT, not a rescue team.
When they get here,
take out the dogs first.
Kill all of them. Do you understand?
If the press ask about the situation...
Dad!
Maintain communication failure.
Stick to a rabid dog story,
not trained military dogs.
I hear you, so please,
just get out of there,
the bridge will collapse.
If you just learned about this,
we can easily make it go away.
Dad! Hurry!
I'll call you back.
Get inside. Hurry.
The bridge's going to collapse.
I'm...
Jung-won Cha, Department
of Security at the Blue House.
I'm sure you must be shocked
from this unexpected disaster.
The rescue effort is hampered
due to the thick fog.
However, I made contact
with the authorities
who are organizing a response team.
Thank God. We're saved.
If you follow my instructions,
we'll all be rescued safely.
Thank God.
What's wrong with the phones?
Why is there no network?
The connection's down
due to the explosion.
The response team is working
on getting the network back up.
What about those dogs attacking people?
Well...
Based on the information I have,
there was an outbreak of rabies
in the military canine unit.
The infected dogs were
ordered to be disposed of,
but escaped due to the crash
while being transferred.
Rabies?
If your loved ones were
affected by this atrocity...
I extend my sincerest condolences.
The dogs looked fine at first.
He's right.
Then they suddenly flipped,
attacking at random like crazy.
What dog has "mad dog"
written on its forehead.
They seem normal at first
wandering around the neighborhood
until they bite you out of the blue.
That's why you call them mad.
Isn't that right?
Is it?
When is the rescue team coming anyway?
These are man-killing dogs.
Shoot on sight.
What's this?
Somebody left behind a good bottle.
Kyung-min, this is something
no one benefits from knowing.
Hey. Can I have a word?
Well. Your manner's changed.
Cut the crap.
You're cooking some scam to fool
everyone but I won't play along.
I heard everything in the car.
How much did I owe you?
$64.40. Asshole.
I'll make sure you get a
patriot's medal, class 1.
A patriot's what?
What the hell is that?
- It's a civilian award.
- An award, my ass.
It's awarded in recognition of
outstanding bravery in saving lives.
The reward is at least $100,000.
You bastard, I may
have no connections...
If you work with me, I
could get you even more.
Listen.
Get out alive, mouth shut,
and the reward's yours.
Maybe buy that gas station and
live comfortably ever after.
Or get torn to pieces by mad
dogs and turned into food.
It's your call.
We arrived at the collapsed bridge.
Team 1 is going in.
Get ready for a presser as
soon as they're rescued.
Yes, sir.
- Help's coming.
- Where?
That's a relief.
What about the dogs?
We searched the perimeter
on arrival but didn't see any.
Looks like they've run away.
Please, out of the bus.
Let's go. Come on.
Wait.
Hold up.
We agreed to take out the
dogs before coming for us.
But they can't see them. We'll
evacuate the survivors first.
The SWAT team's heavily
armed so it'll be safe.
We estimate 30 minutes
to reach the edge.
Move to the edge behind the bus.
Come this way.
Aren't you coming with us?
Get off.
Just leave me here. I beg you.
I said get off.
The dogs... they didn't
run off. They're hiding.
Cut the bullshit and get
out. You're my witness.
No... no! If we leave, we'll all die.
Geez! Don't touch me.
Get up on your feet, bastard.
You're really a handful.
Can't even walk straight?
They never stop hunting the target.
What did you say?
- They never lose their target.
- What?
Bring me my laptop. We have to find it.
Hey, Blue House. The
Doc has lost his marbles.
- Find my laptop... my laptop.
- What laptop?
Resume moving. Swiftly.
What's the matter, Doc?
Wasn't it you?
Yura, I have goosebumps.
- Be quiet for a moment.
- Check the rear.
Yes, sir.
All clear, sir.
Check. Keep moving.
Check!
Secure the evacuees' safety.
Dammit.
Infiltration team.
Come in!
What's going on?
What is that?
Answer me.
Guard the perimeter.
Permission to fire at will.
Die!
My leg, my leg!
Miran.
Bori?
Is that you, Bori?
Honey.
Ma'am!
Honey, no. No!
Kyung-min!
Don't look at me!
Dad...
Kyung-min!
Jodie! Shush, be quiet.
Let me go!
- No, Kyung-min.
- Mom's book's in here.
Let go of the bag.
No.
Get out of here.
Let's go.
Come on, Dad.
The government is taking all possible
measures to rescue those stranded...
Yes, sir.
No one from the SWAT
teams is responding.
The press is waiting outside.
Get in.
You okay, Dad? You're bleeding...
- I'm alright, honey.
- You're bleeding.
Don't worry about it.
The radio!
I'm really sorry. I have
to go back for the radio.
We can't escape without that.
No, I won't let you.
You saw how the bridge was collapsing.
Stay here. Dad will be right back.
The book...
Across the sky these
pretty little toes paddle.
Everything coming together
to make my beautiful baby.
Your books have sold out.
Really? Already?
Yeah, Dad's bought 300 copies,
so they ran out in the bookstores.
What? You bought them all, then?
Jung-won! You come here, honey.
This concludes a book reading session
by the author of "Knock Knock Knock."
Can you turn that down?
Better yet, take it outside.
I'm trying to die in peace
here, and you're not helping.
So much drama in your family.
Don't come up. I want to be left alone.
Geez, you scared me.
You're still alive.
You said the government would save us.
Look where we ended up.
Can you pipe down?
Those dogs... they're trained, right?
I told them everything.
About the medal and the lying.
Anyway, the dogs took
the guns off dead soldiers.
Terrible.
Oh God.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, ma'am.
- It's okay...
- It hurts!
Okay, so now what?
We'll get out of here.
No matter what.
- What then?
- Tell us something we don't know.
How am I supposed
to walk? I've been shot.
Why are you licking the gasoline?
Do you still believe your
dad will come back safely?
We're all gonna die here.
You, me, and your dad too.
Over there.
Do you see that dog there?
That's Echo 9.
E9...
Is that the boss?
Not the boss.
But all of the dogs out there
were cloned from her.
It makes her their mother.
In order...
to make the dogs more brutal,
they killed so many of
her puppies in front of her.
So what she's doing now,
it's not hunting. It's revenge.
She's taking revenge
for her murdered babies.
Come in, Control. Sir?
Is that you, Jung-won?
Can you see us?
You shot that flare, right?
We're starting to move toward Seoul.
No, that way's cut off by toxic gas.
You have to go the other way.
SWAT teams are on standby
at the break in the bridge.
Then, we'll find the
nearest bus to reach them.
We'll travel together on a bus.
Please have snipers
ready to take out the dogs.
We can't use the snipers.
Press and TV cameras will be nearby...
Collect the survivors and get out.
We'll take care of the dogs later.
No. They know everything.
What?
Everyone here knows
about the Silence Project.
We can't cover it up anymore.
I will take them out of here first.
It's Dad.
Dad...
We need to open the door.
- How do you open this door?
- Don't.
How do you open it?
I said don't. Don't you
see the dogs outside?
Geez!
Damn... they are in front of the bus.
It's because of him?
- Who?
- Him.
- What is he doing?
- Don't move!
Kyung-min! Let her go, you bastard.
Dad!
Go away!
Let her go.
- Dad!
- Kyung-min.
Go. Hurry.
- Dad!
- Open this up, bastard.
Kyung-min.
The fire's dying out. Open the door.
Ma'am, Ma'am!
No!
Go away.
Go! Go!
- Ma'am? Ma'am!
- No, no!
Ma'am!
Go away, you dirty dogs.
Dad!
Ew, hot. Don't get any closer.
Hurry.
Open up!
Everyone, close your eyes.
Dad!
Hurry up!
Hurry.
Hey, look at me! Look at Papa.
I'm beating a man, and
I don't feel bad one bit.
Does it hurt? Do you
feel pain, psychopath?
You okay, baby?
- Are you okay, Dad?
- I'm sorry.
Oh, no...
- There's no key.
- What?
Of all the vehicles,
you had to pick the one with no key?
But you have one.
The master key.
Okay, but you can't hold
this against me later.
If you do, I'll kill you.
- It worked.
- Yes, yes, yes!
Back it up towards the airport.
There's a bus moving.
Sir, I asked the military for snipers.
The Head of Military
Intelligence is outside.
The authorities have canceled
the Secretary of Security's briefing
to discuss the bridge collapse and
the subsequent rescue efforts.
All eyes on him how this going to do
for his candidacy for President.
Are you really going to
carry out the rescue?
You have two scenarios:
First, the tragic loss of lives due to
the unexpected collapse of the bridge.
Second, a civilian massacre by attack dogs
authorized by the leading presidential candidate.
The Minister will let you do choose.
Control, we're 10m out
from where the bridge ends.
Control center?
Look. The dogs were waiting for us.
Don't worry. There
are snipers on standby.
Ma'am...
Give it a moment. We'll
get out of here soon.
Control, we're ready to
leave. You may shoot.
Do you read me?
Control!
Why aren't they answering?
The bridge will collapse soon.
Do something or we're dead.
We shouldn't have followed you here.
You're going to lure them out.
You created this situation.
When this jerk lures the dogs away,
you break the back window to get out.
- I'm just a researcher.
- Come on!
I did as I was told...
I followed orders.
Don't do it, Dad. Please!
We should set a trap instead.
Honey.
They're all in. Pull.
Everyone, focus.
On three...
- Get out, Miran. Come on.
- Get out, Kyung-min.
Come on! Go, go, go!
We have to go now.
I can't leave her here.
You have to, sir.
I beg you. Just go.
- I'll hold it. You go.
- No... You go.
Let it go. Come on!
Sir!
- What the... Hell, no!
- Sir!
Get out of there.
- Come on, Blue House!
- Let me go.
No! Let me go.
Sir...
- Sir!
- Let it go, man.
Let it go.
If any of those dogs
get out, we're all dead.
All of us, including your daughter!
You fucking bureaucrat!
Where's our rescue?
The rescue isn't here.
They are not here.
- Want another smack?
- There's no one.
- What? It's just the damn fog.
- They're not here.
Look over there.
They're really not here.
- No?
- You said to come here?
How can we go up there?
What to do...
- My leg is hurt.
- Hey, parachute kid.
You do know who your
dad's been talking to?
Hyun-baek Chung... Hyun-baek Chung...
Good old uncle Hyun-baek...
He's the one that started
this whole Silence Project.
The project was approved by him when
he was on the Defense Commission.
That must have earned him
his seat at the Blue House.
Did you meet him there?
You had no idea.
Sir...
Are you the one
who approved this project?
Is that why you pulled
the rescuers out?
To cover it up?
We are still out here.
Agreed...
I would've done the same if I were you.
The bridge will collapse any minute.
The dogs you want to
bury are on that bridge.
What would benefit you the most?
So you reached a
logical political decision.
After long consideration. I understand.
Still, if you were here...
and saw what happened, then
hell, you couldn't do this.
Listen.
We're heading to Seoul, which
you say is so dangerous
and full of toxic gas.
It'll be one of two things.
Either the bridge will collapse
or the toxic gas will get us.
I just ask for one thing.
If you sent medics and the press
off because of the collapse,
get them back on standby.
Or I'll make you regret it.
Hey, wrecker! That's your truck, right?
Let's go.
I would go with you
but I don't have the key.
My keys are on that bus.
The damn master key...
This is where the cage was before.
I dropped my laptop around here,
It has to be here somewhere.
I can try something with
that. Do you hear me?
My laptop.
I found it. It's here.
Oh, poor Captain Kang...
So you'll lure the dogs into
the cage using your laptop.
Then I retrieve my keys, tow
the cage with my wrecker
and drive through that burning inferno.
- Who's going into the cage?
- I will.
I'm impressed, Blue House.
But what if the plan fails?
It won't, or we'll all die.
Yeah, he's not convinced
either. I don't trust him.
You trust him because you have
to, not because he's worthy of it.
I trust you. So drive properly.
Man, even my mom has never said that.
If you fail, you're making
your daughter an orphan.
You must know that.
Better than being a father
that lost his little girl.
Done.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Get moving.
Dad.
I've been thinking about it...
I don't want to study abroad.
Do you have something to read?
You must keep talking even
after the target's reconfigured.
- Alert me when you're ready.
- Okay.
Kyung-min.
Give me that book. I need
to read something out loud.
You know it's the last copy.
You have to give it back to me.
It won't snap in one swing?
I'm sorry, Yura, for making
you tee off in a place like this.
Distance?
80 yards. No wind.
How come I get the most dangerous task?
If only I double-checked the passport.
Stop whining, because
it's not your fault.
What?
I knew my passport had expired.
I didn't say anything. I
was too afraid too play.
Thus, it's not your fault.
Hey! Hit it.
We haven't got all day.
Change the club.
Let's go with a utility.
A utility can easily
cover that distance.
From now on, no one
except the target speaks.
Okay.
Here we go.
Three, two,
one.
A black cave house behind the bushes.
There's someone's sleeping here.
Give her a signal.
Good shot.
All of these come together...
Whoa... the bridge is rocking.
Dammit.
We're running out of time.
Toss me the ball.
Almost there.
They're coming out.
Such pretty baby eyes
and the soft downy hair.
You did it! Awesome.
Where's the key?
No, Yura. You can't get him off.
Say something, Blue House. You okay?
Hang in there. We're on our way to you.
No, wrecker. Don't come.
Don't come any closer. Stop.
- Hey, kid.
- Dad?
Where are you going? No.
Come back. Hurry.
What do we do? Shit! Blue House.
Wrecker, can you hear me?
- Dad!
- No...
Kyung-min! Are you listening?
With your truck weight on
top this bridge will break.
Don't worry about me.
Just go by yourself.
Sorry for not being there with you...
- Your mom & your wife
I'm sorry, too.
Dad.
Dad!
What the hell... Kyung-min?
Kyung-min.
Kyung-min!
Dad!
Don't move, honey.
Shit! Don't look there.
Go back to the truck! Now!
Listen to your dad for once.
Kyung-min!
Go back to the truck!
Please do as I say.
- Dad!
- Kyung-min.
Kyung-min!
- Dad!
- Kyung-min.
What are you doing? I
told you to wait for me.
You...
Pull, mister!
Pull now.
Got it! Wait.
I said pull.
We got him. Let's go.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
What's that?
Hurry! It's collapsing!
Are you okay?
It's the toxic gas. Cover your mouth.
Don't breathe it in.
Cover your mouth.
Hold on tight!
The cage is gone.
He's gone. I guess he died a hero.
Blue House!
Man, he has nine lives.
He made it.
My truck's a little damaged
but insurance will cover it.
I didn't do this for any
sort of recognition.
You'll get your medal.
They'll reward a great
civil hero... Probably.
Probably?
What do you mean?
Are you going back on your word again?
We were so close.
They're coming.
There's a truck coming.
Any information on the survivors?
Not yet, sir.
Everyone!
Let's welcome the survivors.
By a miracle, they came back
to us from this dire situation.
Jung-won, think about
what matters now...
He's so violent in nature.
Saving its citizens in danger
is a nation's basic duty.
Think about your daughter's future.
She's not going abroad, you son of a...
Scumbag lower than a dog.
I'm Jung-won Cha from the Department
of Security at the Blue House.
Everything that happened on
the bridge has been recorded.
All the evidence about the
Silence Project is on here..
...and on here.
Where are you going? That's
the Secretary of Security.
He's responsible for all this.
And the proof's on here.
Look how he changes his
position so quickly. Amazing...
So you're not going to study abroad?
No. I'll live with my dad.
I devoted myself...
Good thinking.
Besides, why go to
Australia to study music
when you rap in Korean?
And about your dad...
Miran, stop.
You talk too much for
someone who's been shot.
Doesn't it hurt anymore?
Can you please put
her in the ambulance?
I've been shot. Please take me away.
My blood type is AB.
An investigation will be launched
with the information provided by Cha.
The Silence Project was a
classified animal experiment
that involved cloning
and brutal experiments...
...causing a deadly accident
taking more than 100 lives.